

# Mustafa YASAR Amsterdam The Netherlands

myasar0938@gmail.com +31 6 84593322 <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>GitHub</u> Personal Website Full Stack Developer in continuous learning. After working in the Turkish National Police Academy and later as a lawyer, I am finally following my dream and dedicating myself to IT. My biggest goal is to combine the discipline with effective using of time, teamwork and the problem-solving experiences I gained from my past professions. My passions are to work with care, constantly improve myself, ask, learn and help others.

HTML	CSS	Bootstrap	Javascript	GIT
Rest API	Express.js	Node.js	MySQL	React.js

#### **Education**

HackYourFuture, Web Development | Aug. 2022 – Feb. 2023 | Curriculum

A 28-week course designed to cover all aspects of full-stack development including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL and ReactJS.

Anadolu University-Web Design and Development | Sept. 2020

Law Faculty at Gazi University | July 2015 – Aug 2019

Turkish National Police Academy | July 2012 - April 2015

## **Experience**

HackYourFuture-Trainee | Aug 2022 - Mar 2023

Career Break Apr 2021 - May 2022

Lawyer at Celik Law Consultant | July 2019 - Apr 2021

## **Development projects**

Travel2Gether | Feb. 2023 | Demo | Source

Uber Ul Clone | Aug. 2022 | Demo | Source

Quiz App Project | Sept. 2022 | Demo | Source

REST API Project | Nov. 2022 | Demo | Source

#### **Other**

Languages: English, Turkish.

Hobbies: Football, cycling, workout.